

yuniormtr@gmail.com

 \bowtie

https://mariotoribi0.github.io/

0

https://www.linkedin.com/in/mario-t-

(in)

3538aa205/

MARIO TORIBIO

DATA SCIENTIST | TENSORFLOW DEVELOPER

EDUCATION

2016 - 2020

Mechanical Industrial Technician

Instituto Tecnológico San Ignacio de Loyola

2020 - 2024

Mechatronic Engineer

Instituto Tecnológico de Santo Domingo (INTEC)

2023 - 2024

Microdegree, Artificial

Intelligence

Fusemachines

SKILLS

Profesional Skills

- Python
- SQL
- Power BI / DAX Power M
- Tableau
- Javascript
- Visual Basic
- · Web Scraping
- Tensorflow
- Google Cloud Platform
- Matlab
- C/C++
- Docker
- Azure
- MS Office

Personal Skills

Proactive Teamwork

Problem Solver • English •

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

Highly experienced data analysis professional with extensive experience in Tensorflow, Python, SQL, Power BI and Excel. Expert in developing complex dashboards in Power BI, feature engineering and machine learning. Certified as a Tensorflow Developer, with solid knowledge in programming, statistics, data engineering and machine learning. As well as winner of the DATATHON in the Machine Learning challenge in 2023.

EXPERIENCE

Data Scientist - AFP Crecer October 2023 - Actual

- Development and implementation of machine learning models for company solutions.
- Data extraction, cleaning and visualization

Data Analyst - INTEC August 2022 - September 2023

- Collect, clean and analyze large volumes of data with Python and SQL to identify essential KPIs for the organization and generate reports.
- Develop predictive machine learning models to project variables related to KPIs and improve resource allocation strategies.
- Develop complex reports using DAX and Power M in Power BI, as well as Tableau.

Apolo27 (NASA HUMAN EXPLORATION ROVER CHALLENGE) - INTEC
August 2022 - April 2023

• Create machine learning models to estimate crew members' conditions using sensors.

CERTIFICATIONS

- Tensorflow Developer Certificate
- First Place Machine Learning DATATHON 2023
- Machine Learning Specialization Stanford
- Deep Learning Specialization Deep Learning.Al
- Scientific Computing with Python
- SQL (Advanced)